teamunify.com 2014-05-30

# Privacy Policy

Effective Date: January 8, 2013

TeamUnify, LLC, together with its affiliates (“TeamUnify,” the “Company,” “us,” “our,” and “we”), is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit the Company's website (the “TeamUnify Website,” described further below) and individuals who visit Swim Team Websites (defined below) operated by Company (collectively, “Visitors”), as well as entities and individuals who enter into agreements with Company for the purchase of services and/or products and/or register for accounts on the TeamUnify Website and/or Swim Team Websites (collectively, “Customers”). This Privacy Statement describes TeamUnify's information practices in relation to Visitors' and Customers' use of the TeamUnify Website and Swim Team Websites, as well as the purchase of products or services from Company and through the TeamUnify Website and Swim Team Websites. This Privacy Statement also applies to information collected by TeamUnify through offline contacts it may have with Customers and Visitors. Customers and Visitors may at times be referred to in this Privacy Statement as “you.” If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact TeamUnify at info@teamunify.com. 

## Your Agreement to this Privacy Statement

Please read this Privacy Statement carefully before you browse and use TeamUnify's Website or any Swim Team Websites. **Your usage of TeamUnify's Website or any Swim Team Websites signifies that you have read, understand, and agree with all of the terms of this Privacy Statement. If you are acting on behalf of an entity, you represent that you have full authority to bind your entity to this Privacy Statement. If you do not have such authority or if you do not agree to all of the terms of this Privacy Statement, do not use TeamUnify's Website or any Swim Team Website.** You agree that this Privacy Statement is supported by reasonable and valuable consideration, the receipt and sufficiency of which are hereby acknowledged. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you acknowledge that such consideration includes your use of TeamUnify's Website and the Swim Team Websites.

## Modification to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to update and revise this Privacy Statement at any time. We will post any new or revised Privacy Statement here, and you should review this Privacy Statement regularly to make sure that you are aware of its terms. You can determine if this Privacy Statement has been revised since your last visit to TeamUnify's Website or any Swim Team Website by referring to the effective date at the top of this Privacy Statement. TeamUnify will also provide notification of significant changes to this Privacy Statement through TeamUnify's Website and Swim Team Websites. In addition, if changes are significant, we will also notify you of such changes either (a) via the Personal Information (defined below) that you have provided to us, if any; or (b) by requiring that you agree to the revised Privacy Statement the next time you log in to use the TeamUnify Website or any Swim Team Website if you have an account for the same. Your use of TeamUnify's Website or any Swim Team Website following such updates or revisions to this Privacy Statement constitutes your acceptance of and agreement to the terms of this Privacy Statement, as updated or revised by us, and the revisions will apply to the Personal Information and Anonymous Information (defined below) collected on and after the date on which we post the updated or revised Privacy Statement. We will keep prior versions of this Privacy Statement in an archive for your review upon request.

## Websites Covered

This Privacy Statement covers the information practices of Websites owned and operated by TeamUnify, including: http://www.teamunify.com, http://www.teamunifygear.com, and http://www.getoutswim.com (collectively referred to as “TeamUnify's Website” or “the Company's Website”). Teamunify.com is a marketing and sales information source for Company's swim team management platform. Getoutswim.com and Teamunifygear.com are eCommerce websites through which Company sells swim suits, swim related gear and other products.

TeamUnify is a developer of software that helps swim teams better manage themselves. As part of this effort, TeamUnify develops and maintains websites for such swim teams (collectively, “Swim Team Websites”). This Privacy Statement covers the information practices of Swim Team Websites that are operated by TeamUnify. You will know that this Privacy Policy covers the information practices of such Swim Team Websites because the websites will direct you to this Privacy Statement when you click on the privacy links on such websites.

TeamUnify's Website may contain links to other websites. TeamUnify is not responsible for the information practices or the content of such other websites. The Company encourages you to review the privacy statements of other websites to understand their information practices.

## Personal Information Collected

Personally-identifiable information that we may collect includes information such as your name, home or business address, email address, telephone number, fax number, and other information that could be used to contact you or identify you personally; details regarding your entity; and your financial information, such as your credit card and debit card numbers and bank routing and account numbers (hereafter, “Personal Information”). See additional information below regarding collection and use of your Personal Information.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected

As you navigate and browse the Company's Website and/or any Swim Team Websites, TeamUnify automatically collects and stores information about your visit to and use of the Company's Website and/or Swim Team Websites, such as: The date and time of your visit, the duration of your visit, the type of browser and browser language you use, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, the actions you take on the Company's Website and/or Swim Team Websites (such as the web pages viewed and the links clicked), and the websites (if any) from which you linked to the Company's Website and/or Swim Team Websites. All non-personally identifiable information is referred to in this Privacy Statement as “Anonymous Information.” We collect Anonymous Information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and web beacons, which are discussed in more detail below.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal Information may be provided by you to us in several ways, including without limitation, when you contact us through the TeamUnify Website or a Swim Team Website, when you express an interest in obtaining additional information about the services we offer; when you create an account through the TeamUnify Website or any Swim Team Website, or when you purchase products through the TeamUnify Website or a Swim Team Website. In order to engage in any of the foregoing activities, you must provide us your Personal Information.

In order to use certain features of the TeamUnify Website and/or Swim Team Website, or to otherwise participate in the services we offer, you may be asked to provide Personal Information. YOU DO NOT HAVE TO PROVIDE US WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO BROWSE THE TEAMUNIFY WEBSITE OR ANY SWIM TEAM WEBSITE, AND WE ONLY COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM YOU WHEN YOU VOLUNTARILY PROVIDE IT TO US. YOU ARE NEVER UNDER ANY OBLIGATION TO PROVIDE YOUR PSERONAL INFORMATION. However, if you do not provide your Personal Information, you may not be able to use certain features of the TeamUnify Website and Swim Team Websites. When you do provide us your Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Statement.

The Company uses Personal Information of TeamUnify Customers and Visitors to perform the services requested. For example, if you fill out a “Contact Me” web form or if you request a service demonstration, the Company will use the information provided to contact you about your interest in our services, or if you purchase a product, we will use your Personal Information to fulfill the order. We may also use your Personal Information to contact you regarding your account and use of the services.

The Company may also use Personal Information of TeamUnify Customers for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use Personal Information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in TeamUnify, our services, and to send you information regarding the Company and its partners, such as information about promotions or events. At any time, you may request that we stop contacting you for marketing purposes. In such event, however, we reserve the right to contact you for purposes relating to the services and your use of the TeamUnify Website or any Swim Team Website.

The Company uses financial information solely to collect payment for the services and/or products you purchase through the TeamUnify Website or any Swim Team Website.

When you use our OnDeck™ software, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services. Most likely, these controls are located in the device's settings menu. If you have questions about how to disable your device's location services, we recommend that you contact your device manufacturer or your mobile service carrier.

## Collection and Use of Anonymous Information

TeamUnify uses commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and web beacons, to collect Anonymous Information as you navigate the Company's Website and/or Swim Team Websites. This section describes in further detail the types of Anonymous Information the Company may collect and how the Company may use this Anonymous Information.

TeamUnify uses Anonymous Information to operate and improve the Company's Website and/or the Swim Team Websites. We may also use Anonymous Information to track what visitors to Company's Websites and/or the Swim Team Websites are looking at most frequently so we can recognize and deliver more of the desired features, products, and services.

The Company may also combine Anonymous Information with Personal Information about TeamUnify Customers, such as to provide personalized information about the Company to such Customers. We also may use both Personal Information and Anonymous Information to help diagnose problems with the services, to analyze statistical use patterns and demographic data, and to improve our services.

### Cookies

TeamUnify uses a feature of your Internet browser called “cookies” to make your interactions with the Company's Websites and Swim Team Websites easy and meaningful. When you visit the Company's Website and/or any Swim Team Website, TeamUnify's servers send a cookie to your computer. The cookie is placed on your hard drive and it assigns your computer a unique, random number that acts as a sort of anonymous ID. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you; rather, a cookie identifies the computer a Customer or Visitor uses to access the TeamUnify Website and/or any Swim Team Website. A cookie cannot read data off of your hard drive. Unless you choose to identify yourself to TeamUnify, such as by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or filling out a web form, you remain anonymous to the Company when browsing the TeamUnify Website and/or any Swim Team Website; in other words, the cookie alone with not allow us to identify you personally. We may use cookies to remember your personal settings, pre-fill forms for you, and to monitor your use of the TeamUnify Website and/or any Swim Team Website to improve the services and websites.

There are two types of cookies: Session-based and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during one session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer. 

If you have chosen to identify yourself to TeamUnify, the Company uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the Company to uniquely identify you. Each time you log into the service, a session cookie containing an encrypted, unique identifier that is tied to your account is placed on your browser. These session cookies allow the Company to uniquely identify you when you are logged into your account on the TeamUnify Website or a Swim Team Website, and to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies are required to use your account. See additional information below regarding our use of session cookies in the Section entitled “Security.”

TeamUnify uses persistent cookies that only the Company can read and use to identify browsers that have been used to previously visit the Company's Websites and/or any Swim Team Websites. When you set up an account on the TeamUnify Website or any Swim Team Website or otherwise provide the Company with Personal Information, a unique identifier is assigned you. This unique identifier is associated with a persistent cookie that the Company places on your web browser. We are aware that the information stored in persistent cookies needs to be maintained securely and confidentially. For example, the Company does not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. See the Section entitled “Security” below for additional information regarding our security practices.

TeamUnify may use information from session and persistent cookies in combination with Personal Information of TeamUnify Customers to provide such Customers with information about the Company and our services.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can disable the acceptance of cookies at any time by changing the preferences in your browser. Most browsers also allow you to change the settings to require that the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie. If you disable your web browser's ability to accept cookies, you will be able to browse Company's Website and any Swim Team Websites, but you will not be able to successfully use an account on Company's Website or any Swim Team Website or use various other features of Company's Website or any Swim Team Website.

### Web Beacons

TeamUnify uses web beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about Customers and Visitors' usage of the Company's Website and/or Swim Team Websites, as well as Customers' interaction with emails from the Company. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular website tied to the web beacon, and a description of a website tied to the web beacon. For example, TeamUnify may place web beacons in marketing emails that notify the Company when you click on a link in the email that directs you to the Company's Website and/or Swim Team Websites. TeamUnify uses web beacons to operate and improve the Company's Website and Swim Team Websites and email communications. TeamUnify may use information from web beacons in combination with Personal Information about Customers to provide such Customers with information about the Company and our services.

### IP Addresses

When you visit TeamUnify's Website and/or any Swim Team Website, the Company collects your Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses to track and aggregate Anonymous Information. For example, TeamUnify uses IP addresses to monitor the regions from which Customers and Visitors navigate the Company's Website and Swim Team Websites. TeamUnify also collects IP addresses from Customers when they log into Company's Website and/or any Swim Team Website in order to confirm the applicable customer's identity.

### Third Party Cookies and Website Analytics

From time-to-time, TeamUnify engages third parties to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from Visitors and Customers of the Company's Website and Swim Team Websites. TeamUnify may also use other third-party cookies to track the performance of Company advertisements. The information provided to third parties does not include Personal Information; rather, we only provide Anonymous Information. This information may be re-associated with your Personal Information after the Company receives it back from the third parties, but, again, the third parties do not receive your Personal Information. Further, these third-parties are not authorized to use your Anonymous Information in any way other than as described herein and are required to keep the information confidential.

### Public Forums, Refer a Friend, and Customer Testimonials

TeamUnify may provide bulletin boards, blogs, chat rooms, or other areas where users can post information or content for public viewing, on the Company's Website and/or Swim Team Websites. Any Personal Information or other content you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums, and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. Such information and content is not subject to this Privacy Statement; rather, such information and content is subject to Company's Website Terms and Conditions, located here. TeamUnify is not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit in these forums. You should be aware that such content and information may be made broadly available to the public.

Customers and Visitors may elect to use the Company's referral service to inform friends about the Company's Website. When using the referral service, the Company requests the friend's name and email address. TeamUnify will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Company's Website. TeamUnify does not store this information.

TeamUnify posts a list of Customers and testimonials on the Company's Website that contain information such as Customer entity names and the names and titles of key individuals associated with such Customers. TeamUnify obtains the consent of each Customer prior to posting any information on such a list or posting testimonials.

## Sharing of Information Collected

TeamUnify may share Personal Information about Customers and Visitors with the Company's agents so that these agents can contact Customers and Visitors who have provided contact information on our behalf to perform certain services for us, fulfill product orders, perform certain marketing on our behalf, and/or perform website analytics services, as described above. TeamUnify may also share Personal Information of our Customers and Visitors with the Company's agents to ensure the quality of information provided. TeamUnify does not share, sell, rent, or trade Personal Information with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

We distribute products manufactured by TYR and The Finals. If you purchase TYR and/or The Finals products from the TeamUnify Website or any Swim Team Website, we will send your purchase request, along with Personal Information that you are required to submit to order the products, to TYR and/or The Finals, as applicable. These companies will use your Personal Information solely for the purpose of fulfilling your product order, and they will not use or disclose your Personal Information for marketing purposes or otherwise.

TeamUnify uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use financial information or your other Personal Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on the Company's behalf. 

All of the third parties described above are not authorized to use your Personal Information for any purpose other than as described above and are required to keep the Personal Information confidential.

We may transfer any and all Personal Information and Anonymous Information to a third party in the event of a sale or transfer of assets or other disposition of all or any portion of our business. We will make reasonable efforts to notify you when your Personal Information and Anonymous Information is transferred to any third party under this paragraph by posting such notice on the Company Website and Swim Team Websites, and by contacting you via the Personal Information you have provided us, if any. 

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Statement, TeamUnify reserves the right to disclose your Personal Information and Anonymous Information, without your consent and without notice to you, if we reasonably believe we are required by law, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process to do so; if we reasonably believe that disclosure is necessary to protect, establish, or exercise our rights or defend against legal claims; or if we reasonably believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our other Customers or Visitors or our employees, property, or business.

## Correcting and Updating Your Information

TeamUnify Customers (and Visitors who have provided us their Personal Information, such as to contact us with a question) may update or change their Personal Information by editing their user or organization record, or by sending us an email request to info@teamunify.com.

To update a billing profile, please visit your team's Swim Team Website, Sign In, and then click on “Billing Setup.” In addition to updating your billing information, you can also change the form of electronic payment processing you desire. 

If you request that your Personal Information be changed, we may still maintain your preexisting Personal Information for purposes of recordkeeping and to comply with our retention policy described below.

## Individual Customer Data

TeamUnify Customers use our services and their respective Swim Team Website to host data and Personal Information about their swim team and members (“Customer Data”). TeamUnify will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such Customer Data except as provided in this Privacy Statement, in the TeamUnify Master Club Annual Subscription Agreement, or as may be required by law. Individual records of Customer Data may be viewed or accessed for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issues, or suspected violation of the TeamUnify Master Club Annual Subscription Agreement, or as may be required by law. Customers are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of their TeamUnify usernames and passwords.

## Intended Users of the TeamUnify Website

The TeamUnify Website is intended for adults only. By accessing, browsing, or using the TeamUnify Website, you affirm (i) that you are eighteen (18) years old or older, or that you are between the ages of thirteen (13) and seventeen (17) and possess legal parental consent or guardian consent to use the TeamUnify Website and provide information through the TeamUnify Website; and (ii) that you have authority to agree to this Privacy Statement and are competent and capable of understanding and complying with this Privacy Statement. The TeamUnify Website is not directed at children under the age of thirteen (13). TeamUnify does not and will not knowingly permit submission of Personal Information by anyone under thirteen (13) years of age through the TeamUnify Website. TeamUnify does not and will not knowingly contact children under the age of thirteen (13) for marketing purposes.

## Information from Children under Age Thirteen – SWIM TEAM WEBSITEs

We recognize that children under age thirteen (13) may want to register for accounts through and use the Swim Team Websites. Before we allow a child under age thirteen (13) to register for an account through a Swim Team Website or to otherwise provide us Personal Information through use of a Swim Team Website, we first obtain consent from the child's parent or guardian for the child to use the applicable Swim Team Website and provide us Personal Information through the use of the Swim Team Website.

When a child under age thirteen (13) tries to register for an account on a Swim Team Website or otherwise provide us Personal Information through a Swim Team Website, we collect the child's e-mail address (or that of a parent or guardian) solely for the purpose of contacting the parent or guardian to request consent. We send the child and/or parent or guardian an email directed to the parent or guardian and provide the parent or guardian forty-eight (48) hours to respond with his or her consent to allow the child to register for an account on the Swim Team Website or otherwise provide us Personal Information through use of the Swim Team Website. If the parent or guardian refuses to allow the child to register for an account on the Swim Team Website or otherwise provide us Personal Information through the Swim Team Website, or if the parent or guardian does not provide consent within forty-eight (48) hours of when we requested consent, we delete the child's email address (as well as the parent or guardian email address) from our database and do not allow the child to register for an account or otherwise provide us Personal Information through use of the Swim Team Website.

Before allowing a child under age thirteen (13) to use any feature of a Swim Team Website that might result in public disclosure of the child's Personal Information, comments, or content to the public, we require a high level of verification to confirm that the parent or guardian has given permission for the child to participate in such features and activities. For example, we may require the parent or guardian to return by postal mail, fax, or email a signed consent form.

When we know we are going to collect Personal Information from a child under age thirteen (13) in order to allow the child to use a certain feature of the Swim Team Website, we take the following steps to protect the child's privacy:

  * We notify the child's parent or guardian about our information practices with regarding to children, including the types of Personal Information we may collect from children, how we collect that information, the uses to which we may put that information, and whether and with whom we may share that information;
  * In accordance with applicable law, we obtain consent from the child's parent or guardian for the collection and use of Personal Information from the child, and/or for sending information about our products and services to the child directly (see discussion of our procedure for obtaining consent directly above);
  * We limit our collection of Personal Information from the child to no more than is reasonably necessary to allow the child to use the particular feature(s) of the Swim Team Website that the child wants to use; 
  * We provide the child's parent or guardian the option to consent to our collection and use of the child's Personal Information, without consenting to our disclosure of that information to third parties; and
  * Providing the child's parent or guardian access, or the ability to request access, to the Personal Information we have collected from the child and the child's account, as well as the ability to request that the child's Personal Information be changed or deleted. The child's parent or guardian may also provide us notice that the parent or guardian refuses to allow any further collection or use of the child's Personal Information at any time, and that the child's account be deleted.

## Security

TeamUnify uses commercially-reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial security measures to assist in protecting against the loss, misuse, and alteration of Personal Information that is under our control. When the TeamUnify Website and/or any Swim Team Websites are accessed using Internet Explorer version 6.0 or later, Firefox version 2.0 or later, or Safari version 3.0 or later, Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) technology protects your Personal Information using both server authentication and data encryption. These technologies help ensure that your Personal Information is safe, secure, and only available to you through use of your username and password. TeamUnify hosts the TeamUnify Website and Swim Team Websites in a secure server environment that uses firewalls and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. TeamUnify also offers enhanced security features that permit Customers to configure security settings to their level of comfort.

Here are additional security measures we take:

**Physical Security**  
Our production equipment is collocated at a facility that provides 24-hour physical security, redundant electrical generators, and other backup equipment designed to keep servers continually up and running. 

**Data Encryption**  
TeamUnify leverages encryption products to protect customer data and communications, including 128-bit Thawte SSL Certification. The lock icon in the browser indicates that data is shielded from access while in transit. 

**Customer Authentication**  
Customers access the TeamUnify Website and/or Swim Team Websites only with a valid and unique user name and password combination, which is encrypted via SSL while in transmission. Customers are prevented from choosing weak or obvious passwords. Customers must enter their user name and password for each log in.

TeamUnify issues a session cookie only to record encrypted authentication information for the duration of a specific session. The session cookie does not include either the username or password of the Customer. TeamUnify does not use session cookies to store other Personal Information or session information, but instead implements more advanced security methods based on dynamic data and encoded session IDs.

**Operating System Security**  
TeamUnify provides operating system-level security by using a minimal number of access points to all production servers. We protect all operating system accounts with strong passwords, and production servers do not share a master password database. All operating systems are maintained at each vendor's recommended patch levels for security and are hardened by disabling and/or removing any unnecessary users, protocols, and processes. 

**Database Security**  
Whenever possible, database access is controlled at the operating system and database connection level for additional security. Access to production databases is limited to a number of points, and production databases do not share a master password database. 

**Server Management Security**  
TeamUnify employees do not have direct access to the TeamUnify production equipment, except where necessary for system management, maintenance, monitoring, and backups. The TeamUnify engineering team provides all system management, maintenance, monitoring, and backups.

Special notice regarding the security of TeamUnify's OnDeck software application 

Data downloaded into the OnDeck application is not secure and is at risk for potential inadvertent use by a non-authorized person that takes possession of the device on which the OnDeck application has been installed. The OnDeck application requires that a User Login be entered every time a Customer wants to use the application to help improve protection of the data that is stored within the OnDeck application database that resides on the device. However, a Customer may set a preference once signed in that will remember the password by automatically populating the password field. Setting this preference is not recommended and will make the device less secure. Customers will be warned of this again when they go to set the user preference. Customers are solely responsible for protecting the security of their devices and the downloaded data on their device. TeamUnify is not responsible or liable for the loss of a device and the stored data and/or inadvertent use by another party.

Unfortunately, no data storage system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers or any Personal Information provided to us in connection with your use of the TeamUnify Website or any Swim Team Website.

## Security Researchers: TeamUnify Vulnerability Reporting Policy

Security researchers seeking information on how to report security issues to TeamUnify should review and comply with the following:

TeamUnify acknowledges the valuable role that independent security researchers play in Internet security. Keeping our Customers' and Visitors' data secure is important to us, and we encourage responsible reporting of any vulnerabilities that may be found in our services, the TeamUnify Website, and/or any Swim Team Website. TeamUnify is committed to working with the security community to verify and respond to any potential vulnerabilities that are reported to us. Additionally, TeamUnify pledges not to initiate legal action against security researchers for penetrating or attempting to penetrate our systems as long as they adhere to the following conditions.

**Testing for Security Vulnerabilities**  
Conduct all vulnerability testing against demonstration websites of our online services to minimize the risk to our Customers' and Visitors' data. Contact and request domain names for demonstration websites at security@teamunify.com.

**Reporting a Potential Security Issue**  
Privately share details of the suspected vulnerability with TeamUnify by sending an email to security@teamunify.com. Provide full details of the suspected vulnerability so TeamUnify may validate and reproduce the issue.

TeamUnify does not permit the following types of research:

  * Causing, or attempting to cause, a Denial of Service (DoS) condition.
  * Accessing, or attempting to access, data or information that does not belong to you.
  * Destroying or corrupting, or attempting to destroy or corrupt, data or information that does not belong to you.

The TeamUnify Commitment to Security Researchers:

To all security researchers who follow this TeamUnify Vulnerability Reporting Policy, TeamUnify commits to the following:

  * To respond in a timely manner, acknowledging receipt of your report
  * To provide an estimated time frame for addressing the vulnerability
  * To notify the reporting individual when the vulnerability has been fixed

**No Compensation**  
TeamUnify does not compensate people for reporting a security vulnerability, and any requests for such compensation will be considered a violation of the conditions above. 

### Retention and Storage

We may retain Personal Information and Anonymous Information in our databases in accordance with any existing document retention policies and applicable laws. This period may extend beyond your relationship with us, but it will be only as long as is necessary, in our discretion, to comply with any applicable law, rule, regulation, or guideline; to prevent fraudulent activity; to protect ourselves against liability; and to allow us to pursue available remedies and limit any damages we may sustain.

### Links

This Privacy Statement applies only to Personal Information and Anonymous Information collected through the TeamUnify Website and Swim Team Websites. The TeamUnify Website and Swim Team Websites may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us (“Linked Sites”). We are not responsible for and have not reviewed the privacy practices of the Linked Sites, or the owners or operators of the Linked Sites. The owners and operators of the Linked Sites may have their own policies regarding privacy and security. We advise you to review any Linked Sites for their own privacy practices to determine what information about you may be collected and used when you use such Linked Sites.

### Severability

If any part of this Privacy Statement is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision, and the remainder of the Privacy Statement shall continue in full force and effect.

### Contacting Us

Questions regarding this Privacy Statement or the information practices pertaining to the Company's Website and/or any Swim Team Websites should be directed to TeamUnify at PO Box 2321, Bend, OR 97709 or info@teamunify.com.

© 2013 TeamUnify, LLC. All rights reserved.
